http://angelamoore.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Hand Painted Jewelry & Fashion
Search:
Privacy Policy
Angela Moore, Inc. assures you that your information is confidential & proprietary and will not be forwarded to outside sources. We collect statistical information on the pages our customers access or visit and information that is voluntarily provided by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. This information may be combined with other identifiable personal information (such as demographic and past purchase information) from our records and other sources and will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information about orders they have placed online. The information we collect, as well as information about your order, is not shared with any organizations.
Angela Moore, Inc. collects the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail. Angela Moore, Inc. will use your e-mail address to send you notification of special events, promotions and exclusive discounts. However, if you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please change your preferences at the following location.
All marketing emails from Angela Moore, Inc. include instructions on how to unsubscribe from future e-mailings.
Use of cookies
A cookie is a small piece of information that web sites use to recognize data about users. Angela Moore Inc. uses two types of cookies to recognize our registered users and to remember their shopping list.
Angela Moore, Inc. uses session ID cookies, once the browser is closed the cookie is terminated. While visiting, these cookies store information such as your shopping cart information to simplify checkout. Session ID cookies do not contain any personal information.
Angela Moore, Inc. uses persistent cookies to identify a registered user, the only information stored in the cookie is the registration number of the user. These cookies remain on the hard drive of a PC and are used to identify users as an existing web-site shopper. You can disable cookies at any time by using your browser options.
Each time you visit or our web site, our web server does not automatically collect any personal information.
Angela Moore, Inc. provides registered users with access to their personal information (e.g., customer number or password), contact information (e.g., email address, name, address and phone number). The personal information can be changed at any time and can be removed at any time by the individual.
Secure shopping
When sensitive information such as credit card, financial and personal information, is sent and received, all visitors are directed to a secure server. Our secure browser technology ensures that no one outside of our professional staff will have access to your credit card information. The angelamoore.com web site makes use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt all credit card and billing information. Your computer must be SSL-enabled to ensure secure transfer of your credit card information.
Angela Moore, Inc. takes reasonable precautions to safeguard personal information transmitted between visitors and the Site. Despite all efforts, however, we may be unable to prevent and shall not be responsible for unauthorized access to such information by third parties.
Ad servers
Angela Moore, Inc. has no partnership or special relationships with any ad-server companies at this time. Should this become true the privacy policy will be updated and all registered users notified.
Each time you visit or our web site, our web server does not automatically collect any personal information.
The angelamoore.com site is designed for use with the latest versions of Internet Explorer (4 and higher), Netscape Navigator (4 and higher) and AOL (4 and higher). If you currently use older versions of these browsers, you may experience technical difficulties with online ordering.
On odd occasions Angela Moore, Inc. may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. We may periodically make changes to the privacy policy, so please check back periodically to review the policy.
If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, as it may be amended from time to time, in whole or part, please do not continue using this Site.
Please direct any inquires to:.
Angela Moore, Inc.
Newport Corporate Park
Two Corporate Park, Suite 301
Middletown, RI 02842
Telephone: 401-849-1900
Email: angela@angelamoore.com
Site Map
Search Terms
Advanced Search
Orders and Returns
Contact Us
Angela Moore, Inc.
Founded in 1997, the Angela Moore collections of hand painted jewelry, resort fashions and home accents are based around "making everyday living an art." Angela Moore has also created "The New ETQ," which offers etiquette and style tips for dining, dressing and decorating.
About Angela Moore
Angela Moore is known for her colorful hand painted jewelry, accessories and resort fashions and her designs are favorites of collectors around the world.
Angela’s philosophy is to “make everyday living an art by celebrating your own individual style.” Read
More
About Our Products
The Angela Moore collection features hand painted, beaded jewelry, resort fashions, colorful accessories and home décor products.
Angela Moore designs include best selling, hand painted jewelry in themes inspired by favorite colors, fun trends and causes we care about.
Causes We Care About
Angela Moore creates hand painted jewelry and accessories for national and regional organizations who share our spirit of giving back..
View Causes We Care About Details
Contact Us for more information about creating beaded jewelry, men’s ties, scarves, etc for your special cause.
Angela Moore, Inc.
Newport Corporate ParkTwo Corporate Place - Suite 301Middletown, RI 02842
Select a State...
Sign up to see new arrivals and promotions.
Sign Me Up!
Request A Catalog
and get inspired...
Can We Help?
© 2015 Angela Moore. All Rights Reserved.
|
Web Design and SEO by: Pinwheel Media
To top
